{
    "word parameters": {
        "excluded": [
            "abuse",
            "abused",
            "abusing",
            "assault",
            "assaulted",
            "assaulting",
            "rape",
            "raped",
            "raping",
            "molest",
            "molested",
            "molesting",
            "suicide",
            "suicidal",
            "kill",
            "killer",
            "killing",
            "update",
            "edit",
            "UPDATE:",
            "edit:"
        ],
        "minimum length question": "32",
        "maximum length question": "500",
        "minimum length answer": "32",
        "maximum length answer": "400"
    },
    "before": {
        "mean length of answer": "84.16923076923077",
        "mean length of question": "220.68307692307692",
        "mean answer score": "317.05846153846153",
        "std answer score": "451.9722383892137",
        "std question": "174.4745461437599",
        "std_answer": "72.59755648161027",
        "max answer score": "3830",
        "longest answer": "804",
        "longest question": "1219",
        "min answer score": "3",
        "shortest answer": "31",
        "shortest question": "10",
        "number of items": "325"
    },
    "after": {
        "mean length of answer": "82.38118811881188",
        "mean length of question": "185.81683168316832",
        "mean answer score": "308.7821782178218",
        "std answer score": "475.1938760973292",
        "std question": "107.16287739208884",
        "std_answer": "57.53800502581533",
        "max answer score": "3830",
        "longest answer": "346",
        "longest question": "498",
        "min answer score": "20",
        "shortest answer": "32",
        "shortest question": "38",
        "number of items": "202"
    }
}